DMC
Mommy? Where are you?
Dear Kureha, I'm going to send her back through the door.
Don't worry about us, okay?
We'll be fine.
Who is Mommy talking about?
What door does she mean?
You were the one who found and saved Kureha that day.
I cannot and will not allow my daughter's precious friend to be excluded.
Well, someday I promise the time will come when bears and people can be friends forever.
Take this pendant with you, sweetie.
It's a love charm.
I know it will help you the way it helped me.
From the beginning, we hated you.
But also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you.
So we had to cross the wall.
Kyurikuma!
Kyurikuma Horashi!
You
That was like way too close I thought you were a bear and almost like shot you
Seriously be more careful
Lou thought she was like way busted like excuse me
So what's that truck? It's like way special vehicle. We just developed for bear annihilation
We cyber guys the dead bear and are like using her to generate electricity now. Yeah, we're fighting fire with fire and bears with bears
Oh
So what about you have you come across any bears around here?
Another one's like been reported apparently someone near school way saw a bear this morning
Lulu hasn't seen anything
Really? Yeah, totally really not this girl. Lulu hasn't seen one single bear growl if you keep stupidly walking around by yourself like this
The bears are going to eat you, too. You should try to be like way more careful
Oh wow talk about a close call growl
Anyway, obviously it's not here either. What the wonders where to look next?
Huh, I don't understand it. Why did Lulu Yurigasaki betrayed Ginko Yurishiro? I'm bare shocked by the whole thing
It's inconsistent. I thought what she wanted was for Ginko Yurishiro's love to be returned to her her actions are contradictory
You are so dense. It's because Ginko Yurishiro is loved by Lulu Yurigasaki
Sparkle Sparkle love is varied and comes in more than one form love is special
Perhaps that's why Kumaria questions everyone who wants to go beyond severance real love has the power to endure
The question stands is your love the real thing?
Then she laid down a ladder for them connecting the two worlds together once more
There they found a single vast mirror standing like a wall in their path
Each girl saw her own reflection in the mirror
They heard Kumaria's voice say
Now your friend is waiting just on the other side of that very door
The wall of severance has like broken down
If you smash the you in the mirror to bits
If you tear yourself apart
She shall grant you a promise kiss
But beware
This may cost you your life
I will ask you one more time
Is your love the real thing?
I found it!
Yay!
The girls stared at themselves in the mirror for a very long time
This is the rest of mom's book
This is the future she wanted to tell me about
The girls stared at themselves in the mirror for a very long time
The moon girl summoned all her courage
I want to cross the sky
So I will smash that mirror
I will smash my image
The forest girl steeled herself as well
I want to cross the sky
So I will destroy that mirror
I will tear my image to shreds
My love is true
With that, the mirror shattered in an instant
And they each found their friends standing there on the other side
The two girls walked slowly up to each other
And simply, wordlessly, gave one another their promised kisses
And so, having completed their promised kiss
The two began a journey beyond Severance
Guided by the Star of Love
This is our destiny?
Our rightful future?
Ginko and I?
Will go beyond Severance?
A bear and a human
That future isn't possible
There's no way
Yes?
Hello?
Hold on
Hey, that's my mom's
Lulu came to give it back
But she should go now
No, wait
Um, I just
You could
Take a bath
You know, before you go
Is it nice?
My mom used to wash my hair like this back when I was a kid
I found out who was behind her death
Miss Yurika ate my mother
She was a bear disguised as a human too
Like you guys
But now she's dead
May I ask you something?
Sure
I know that Mitsuko Yurizono was the one who killed Sumika
So I just
I can't figure out why Ginko told me she was the one who did it
Oh
It's because Ginko thinks it's her fault, Growl
What?
Mitsuko did it
But Ginko still knew that Mitsuko was going to eat Sumika
And she didn't save her
She couldn't make herself
What do you mean?
She loves you with all her heart
So she wanted your love in return
But with Sumika still in your life
She wouldn't be able to get that love
Ginko was jealous of Sumika
But Lulu is no better than her
Because Lulu was a silly jealous bear
She betrayed Ginko
And told on her
Ginko is why Sumika's dead
She helps the killer
Lulu felt like you'd stolen Ginko's love from her
Isn't that crazy?
After Lulu wished so long for you two to have your promised kiss
She went and messed it all up
Lulu sorry
Big time
Well look at that
Guess mom's pendant really was the key
See?
That proves you were friends, right?
Ginko won't lie to you, Growl
There's no way
And you want to know why?
Because you are her precious friend
She thinks I'm her precious friend
Growl, growl
Were we?
Did you unforget something?
Hope so
It's no good
I still can't remember
Except
Well there is one thing that keeps coming up
I know for sure mom told me Ginko was my friend
And when I was little
I sang the love song with a friend I loved
So that friend must have been Ginko
But now I...
How could I simply forget someone I cared about?
None of this makes sense at all
Why?
Why are my only missing memories the ones of Ginko?
Something must have happened between us
But what?
Curry pie
What's important is Ginko loves you anyway
Then and now
Ginko doesn't back down on love
What do you say?
Do you think you can forgive her?
Oh, Growl
Can you try though?
Will you try to be her friend again?
Will you please try to love her again?
I can't
I'm sorry, Lulu
Humans and bears
We have severance between us
No one can overcome it
Lulu guesses you're right
Lost love never comes back
Listen, Kureha, you're in trouble
A bear has been, like, targeting you
Ginko, Yurishiro, and Lulu, Yurigasaki
They're really bears in disguise
We just found evidence that proves it
One of them must be the bear you shot at on the roof
To one you missed
Which means you're, like, way in danger
She's bound to come for her revenge
Call us the second you sense a bear nearby
We'll come take care of it for you
Okay?
Yes, I understand
It's there
Attack!
I don't want to be alone
Who's there?
They must have caught on
Too late
She won't get away
Growl?
Hurry, Pi, why are you helping Lulu?
I don't know
I guess I just feel like this is the right thing to do
Search all corners of the neighborhood
And set the trap
Hey, Lulu just had an idea
She thinks she might know the reason you lost your memory
Why you forgot Ginko
Really?
For a bear to become a girl
She has to make a deal
A deal?
With whom?
With what stands between humans and bears
The wall of severance
The wall
You mean those men
The ones on the phone?
Yes
If they grant a bear Yuri approval in court
She can become a girl
But to do that
You have to let go of something
It's usually whatever you care about the most
What does that mean?
Well, and this is just Lulu's theory
But Lulu bets in Ginko's trial
When they made her let go of something
She had to let go of your love
What?
My love?
Right
She had to give up on the love you gave her
All those years ago
Lulu thinks that's the reason
Ginko disappeared from your memory
That's awful
Lulu's so clever
Don't you think?
Yeah
Lulu's pretty sure you can get it back
Get what back?
Your love for Ginko
Because you didn't actually give up on love
At least that's what Lulu believes
And now
This really is goodbye
Lulu?
Lulu Yurigasaki has revealed the secret of transformation to a third party
For the offending bear
Yuri approval is terminated immediately
Aww
Can't we just give her a break?
Absolutely not
Rules are rules and rules are cool
Oh Lulu
Is that you?
Growl growl growl
Lulu's sorry curry pie
She wasn't supposed to tell you the truth
So now the court won't let her be a girl anymore
Aww
We can't be together ever again
Goodbye curry pie
I found you
Fire!
Fire it now!
It's not them!
This bear is different
What?
Curry pie?
I won't do it
I'll never let a friend be excluded
Hello?
Who's out there calling to me?
I don't know where you are
There is one way to make your wish come true
In the center of the sky is a place called the Door to Friendship
If your love is true, your friend will be waiting for you
You'll find her on the other side of that door
That's it!
The door to friendship
Just like the picture I saw in Mom's book
I met Ginkgo on the other side
Curry pie?
It is!
I know it!
Hello?
I think I heard someone out here calling me
Who are you?
What do you want?
Girl?
Are you the one who's been calling me?
It's okay
You and I can be friends, so you don't have to be alone anymore.
That's right. This is it. This is where it all began.
That day, I crossed the Wall of Severance and met Ginkgo.
I remember now. Ginkgo, you really were my friend. And I... I do love you.
You can get to the other side of the Wall through here, Lulu. You can go safely back to the Bear World.
Fairy Pie?
Growl, growl. Please tell Lulu she finally managed to become your friend.
Sorry, but... No, you are still not my friend, Lulu.
I told you, I will never forgive the Bears. If I see you again, I'll shoot you.
I'll shoot straight and I know I'll kill you.
Lulu gets it.
Go. Get out of here now. And don't you ever come back, either.
You belong over there.
Goodbye.
I... I had to do the right thing.
I knew the evil would end up being you.
I saw what you did.
Who knew this door would be like a way secret passage through the Wall of Severance?
You're the traitor who brought Bears into our school.
You joined the Bears, admit it!
All this time, you've been taking revenge on us for excluding you!
That's not true!
Oh, Kureha Tsubaki.
It's all over now.
And you're gonna, like, pay for taking our friends' lives.
All right!
The hunt's just getting started!
I found her.
I'm going to eat that girl.
Growl, growl.
Howdy.
The hunt.
The thing that does happen now.
I fell inside.
Why mean?
I don't think it's coming, love, to be like.
I didn't try.
Your hunting will find us in the next one.
Howdy.
The hunt for big breaths that will have fallen.
Probably win this Natasha.
This one.
Well, when it comes last, it follows you.
Have a great versucht I've made.
Bypay the two shows you like.
This is a gift like a spider gem.
Let the Yuri trial begin!